// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Why Solar System is named as Solar System?",
    answer: "Latin word for Sun, solis, and anything related to the Sun we call solar",
    options: [
      "Name has taken from Dictionary randomly",
      "Latin word for Sun, solis, and anything related to the Sun we call solar",
      "They got inspiration from Saturn",
      "They got inspiration from any other galaxy"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Solar System in located in which galaxy?",
    answer: "Milky Way Galaxy",
    options: [
      "Andromeda Galaxy",
      "Whirpool Galaxy",
      "Pinwheel Galaxy",
      "Milky Way Galaxy"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "How many moons are there in Solar System?",
    answer: "200+",
    options: [
      "100+",
      "300+",
      "200+",
      "75+"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which two planets don't have their moon?",
    answer: "Mercury & Venus",
    options: [
      "Uranus & Neptune",
      "Mercury & Venus",
      "Mars & Jupiter",
      "Saturn & Earth"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Neil Armstrong, landed on the moon for the first time. He was followed by?",
    answer: "Edwin Aldrin",
    options: [
      "Neil Armstrong",
      "Michael Collins",
      "Edwin Aldrin",
      "None of These"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "How many phases does Moon has?",
    answer: "8",
    options: [
      "10",
      "12",
      "8",
      "7"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Most planetary moons probably formed from the discs of _____",
    answer: "dust & gas",
    options: [
      "rock",
      "dust & gas",
      "metal & soil",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Neil Armstrong, landed on the moon for the first time on ______",
    answer: "July 21, 1969",
    options: [
      "September 18, 1980",
      "July 23, 1969",
      "June 22, 1939",
      "July 21, 1969"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Basically Stars Year is counted in ______",
    answer: "Millions",
    options: [
      "Millions",
      "Thousands",
      "Billions",
      "Trillions"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Distance between Earth and Mars is ______",
    answer: "316 Million km",
    options: [
      "200 Million km",
      "279 Million km",
      "334 Million km",
      "316 Million km"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which Planet is having most Moons in Solar System?",
    answer: "Saturn",
    options: [
      "Saturn",
      "Jupiter",
      "Uranus",
      "Neptune"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Ursa Major is a ______",
    answer: "Constellation",
    options: [
      "Star",
      "Constellation",
      "Satellite",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Which star is nearest to the Earth",
    answer: "Sun",
    options: [
      "Pole Star",
      "Orion",
      "Cassiopeia",
      "Sun"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which planet is called morning star or evening star?",
    answer: "Venus",
    options: [
      "Mars",
      "Venus",
      "Jupiter",
      "Mercury"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "_____ appears as a bright head with a long tail. The tail grows in size as it approaches the sun",
    answer: "Comet",
    options: [
      "Asteroid",
      "Comet",
      "Planet",
      "Meteor"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Read The Following Sentences Carefully, And Choose The Correct One:",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Uranus is mainly made up of hydrogen and helium.",
      "Uranus was the first planet to have been discovered with the help of a telescope.",
      "Saturn has the maximum number of satellites of all the planets in the solar system.",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Which planet appears to be yellowish?",
    answer: "Saturn",
    options: [
      "Asteroids",
      "Mars",
      "Uranus",
      "Saturn"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "The Constellation which consists of 7 main stars is ______",
    answer: "Ursa Major",
    options: [
      "Ursa Major",
      "Leo Major",
      "Hercules",
      "Cassiopiea"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "The first Indian Artificial Satellite was ______",
    answer: "Aryabhatta",
    options: [
      "INSAT",
      "Kalpana-I",
      "Aryabhatta",
      "IRS"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "The first of a month is the new moon day. On 15th day of the same month, which of the following would represent the pahase of the moon day",
    answer: "Full Moon",
    options: [
      "Full Moon",
      "Half Moon",
      "Crescent Moon",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 21,22,23,24,25,26,27,28,29.....
  //   {
  //   numb: 21,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
  // Q20. The first of a month is the new moon day. On 15th day of the same month, which of the following would represent the pahase of the moon day
  //options:
  // crescent moon, half moon, full moon, none of these
];